https://www.naagtag.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

Privacy Policy | Naag Tag Inc. Name Tag and Engraving Company
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
0
You have no items in your shopping cart.
E-mail: naagtag@naagtag.com
Search:
Name TagsBlank Name TagsFast Name TagsLogo Name TagsText Name TagsLogo and Text Name TagsPrinted & Engraved Name TagsPremium Name TagsCustom Shaped Name TagsReusable Name TagsLuggage TagsPet Name TagsWooden Name TagsName Tag AccessoriesFonts for Name Tags and Name PlatesColors List for Name TagsLeather Name TagsPre-Logoed TagsColor Street Name TagsSports Club Name TagsDAR - Daughters of the American Revolution Name TagsdoTERRA Name TagsEpiscopal Church Name TagsFirst Wesleyan Church Name TagsGideons International Name TagsLDS Temple Worker Name TagsMasonic Lodge Name TagsScouting Name TagsUnited Way Name TagsUsher Name TagsName PlatesFast Name PlatesLogo Name PlatesText Name PlatesLogo and Text Name PlatesStandard Name PlatesName Plate HoldersWedged Name PlatesTent & L-Shaped Name PlatesBlank Name PlatesOffice SignsDoor and Hallway SignsRestroom Signs - Bathroom SignsADA Compliant Restroom SignsBasic Engraved Restroom SignsCreative Restroom SignsMirror Acrylic Restroom Symbols / Bathroom SymbolsID BadgesPhoto ID BadgesID Badge AccessoriesID Badge HoldersPlain LanyardsCustom Screen Printed LanyardsClear Plastic Name Tag HoldersPlain LanyardsCustom Printed LanyardsPlaques & AwardsCertificate PlaquesIndividual Recognition PlaquesPerpetual PlaquesScouting PlaquesSpecialty GiftsCustom KitchenwarePersonalized Home DécorPersonalized HardwarePersonalized Journals and CardsChristmas OrnamentsLDSHome GoodsMissionary ItemsPlaques & AwardsPuzzles, Coins, & KeychainsLDS Temple ProductsCovid Safety
Categories
Name TagsBlank Name TagsFast Name TagsLogo Name TagsText Name TagsLogo and Text Name TagsPrinted & Engraved Name TagsPremium Name TagsCustom Shaped Name TagsReusable Name TagsLuggage TagsPet Name TagsWooden Name TagsName Tag AccessoriesFonts for Name Tags and Name PlatesColors List for Name TagsLeather Name TagsPre-Logoed TagsColor Street Name TagsSports Club Name TagsDAR - Daughters of the American Revolution Name TagsdoTERRA Name TagsEpiscopal Church Name TagsFirst Wesleyan Church Name TagsGideons International Name TagsLDS Temple Worker Name TagsMasonic Lodge Name TagsScouting Name TagsUnited Way Name TagsUsher Name TagsName PlatesFast Name PlatesLogo Name PlatesText Name PlatesLogo and Text Name PlatesStandard Name PlatesName Plate HoldersWedged Name PlatesTent & L-Shaped Name PlatesBlank Name PlatesOffice SignsDoor and Hallway SignsRestroom Signs - Bathroom SignsADA Compliant Restroom SignsBasic Engraved Restroom SignsCreative Restroom SignsMirror Acrylic Restroom Symbols / Bathroom SymbolsID BadgesPhoto ID BadgesID Badge AccessoriesID Badge HoldersPlain LanyardsCustom Screen Printed LanyardsClear Plastic Name Tag HoldersPlain LanyardsCustom Printed LanyardsPlaques & AwardsCertificate PlaquesIndividual Recognition PlaquesPerpetual PlaquesScouting PlaquesSpecialty GiftsCustom KitchenwarePersonalized Home DécorPersonalized HardwarePersonalized Journals and CardsChristmas OrnamentsLDSHome GoodsMissionary ItemsPlaques & AwardsPuzzles, Coins, & KeychainsLDS Temple ProductsCovid Safety
Home
>
Privacy Policy | Naag Tag Inc. Name Tag and Engraving Company
×
Login Form
E-mail address *
Password *
Forgot Password ?
Login
or registration
×
Registration
Profile Informations
First Name *
Last Name *
Subscribe to Newsletter
or login
First name is required!
Last name is required!
First name is not valid!
Last name is not valid!
This is not an email address!
Email address is required!
This email is already registered!
Password is required!
Enter a valid password!
Please enter 6 or more characters!
Please enter 16 or less characters!
Passwords are not same!
Terms and Conditions are required!
Email or Password is wrong!
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Naag Tag Inc. - Name Tag and Engraving Company uses and protects any information
that you give Naag Tag Inc. - Name Tag and Engraving Company when you use this website.
Naag Tag Inc. - Name Tag and Engraving Company is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.
Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website,
then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Naag Tag Inc. - Name Tag and Engraving Company may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,
and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we
think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website
according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure,
we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure
the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive.
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit
a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application
can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about
your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic
and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical
analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful
and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you,
other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies.
Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting
to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links
to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website.
Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst
visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.
You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate
that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes,
you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at
naagtag@naagtag.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission
or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information
about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998.
A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to
6796 South Airport Road
West Jordan, UT 84084.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete,
please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address.
We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE name
COOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
About
Naag Tag Inc. is an engraving company specializing in name tags, name plates, license plate frames, custom signs, wall plaques, and Latter-Day Saint (LDS) Products. One of our specialties is making products in full color, such as name badges, photo IDs, etc. We show our quality with every product we make. All of our products including our office signs, name tags, wall plaques, and license plate frames are made in house so we can offer you the best prices in the industry. If you can dream it, we can make it.
Newsletter
Information
About Us
Blog
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
RSS
Company Policies
Call us now: Local: (801) 562-9400 Toll Free: (800) 242-6224 Fax: (801) 562-9408
© 2013 NAAG Tag. All Rights Reserved.
More Magento Furniture Templates at TemplateMonster.com
